<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Pots Pans &amp; Parkers</title>
    <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers" />
    <updated>2019-08-23T20:57:05-06:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Katie Parker</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers</id>

    <entry>
        <title>BABY BROOKLYN’S ARRIVAL</title>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Parker</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/baby-brooklyns-arrival/"/>
        <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/baby-brooklyns-arrival/</id>

        <updated>2019-07-04T14:06:35-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/7/IMG_6587-605x403.jpg" alt="" />
                    Jan 24th 10:30pm I was folding laundry in bed and I noticed that&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/7/IMG_6587-605x403.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><strong>Jan 24<sup>th</sup> 10:30pm</strong></p>
<p>I was folding laundry in bed and I noticed that my contractions were becoming somewhat regular, about 5 minutes apart. They weren’t super strong and felt just like the Braxton Hicks that I had been experiencing for the last 2 months. The contractions stopped after an hour and I went to bed with the nagging feeling like I needed to finish packing my hospital bag- but I didn’t.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Jan 25<sup>th</sup> – 37w6d</strong></p>
<p>My water broke at 12:06am. I woke Jack up from a deep sleep and told him to start gathering a few things because I didn’t have everything ready to go (procrastination much?) I felt about 10 pounds lighter after my water broke and it was such a relief. After running around like chickens with our heads cut off for a half hour, we were on our way to the hospital. I had big plans for my “last meal” as I knew that I would be induced at 39 weeks (Feb 2<sup>nd</sup>). I wanted a big IHOP breakfast and I was going to stuff my face. Instead, I was eating a PB&amp;J and chugging a protein drink before the HANGER set in.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>12:40am</strong></p>
<p>We were immediately admitted into L&amp;D because it was extremely obvious that my water broke and I was in labor. Yay for skipping triage! My contractions were irregular and not very strong, but I was dilated 3cm and fully effaced so we were on our way. The hours pasted by quickly, but every check showed that I hadn’t made much progress on my own. We tried walking the hallways and the peanut ball, but no luck.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>3:30am</strong></p>
<p>I was told that it would be good to get started with a batch of Pitocin. I was at 3.5cm and the contractions were starting to get stronger, but still bearable. I heard horror stories of how painful contractions were with Pitocin so I told my nurse that I needed an epidural before we started the medication. The epidural was done about an hour later and it was wonderful. Advice for first time moms: EPIDURALS DON’T HURT. Seriously! I felt the smallest amount of pressure and that was it. Shortly after that, we started the Pitocin.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>8:00am</strong></p>
<p>My contractions became very regular after the medication. I could feel deep pressure during every contraction and it gradually became more painful (epidurals take away sharp pain- not pressure).</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>9:30am</strong></p>
<p>At this point I was dilated to a 4.5, getting tired, and discouraged. The pressure was so intense and often at this point that I felt like I couldn’t do it. I thought I had hours ahead of me before I was ready to push. I apologized to my mom for what she was about to hear because I needed some intense pop punk music to get me through each contraction. Jack turned up some A Day To Remember and is gave me just enough motivation to make it through each contraction every two minutes.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>10:15am</strong></p>
<p>This is when I really started to doubt myself. I cried when Jack would tell me that another contraction was coming because I feared that deep pressure. Everyone says it feels like you need to poop- no, no – it feels like a bowling ball needs to come out of your butt. But surprise surprise! I was dilated to a 10! Now all of that pressure made sense. The nurse said the baby’s head was low and we would start pushing at 10:30am. My confidence came back at this point and I felt like I was ready to do this.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>10:47am</strong></p>
<p>I pushed 6 times before baby Brooklyn made her appearance and the moment that they laid her on my chest I forgot about all of the pain. 6 pounds 7 ounces, 18.5 inches long, cone head and all! My doctor made the comment that my placenta was beat up and looked like a 42 week placenta. No surprise! My body beat that thing up like nothing else week after week. I started having flash backs to all of the fertility clinic visits, the day that I found out that I was pregnant, and all of the ER trips. So many emotions flooded my mind and everything felt so surreal. I couldn’t believe that we made it through this pregnancy. Brooklyn Elaine is a true miracle.</p>
<p> </p>
<h4 id="mcetoc_1dev9c2b30">HERE IS A LIST OF THINGS THAT SURPRISED ME ABOUT LABOR, RECOVERY AND HAVING A NEWBORN.</h4>
<ul>
<li>Once your water breaks, it doesn’t stop. It will continue to come out with every contraction. My advice: have some adult diapers on hand to wear on your way to the hospital. Life saver!</li>
<li>Your IV will make you swell! Duh, pumping your body full of more fluid!</li>
<li>Bring your own pillow! I was so much more comfortable because of this and I slept way better during recovery.</li>
<li>You thought you were tired during your pregnancy? Um no. You will be more exhausted than you’ve ever been in your entire life. Just be prepared with a stock pile of caffeinated beverages.</li>
<li>Finally, taking care of a little person is freaking hard! But, holding your baby that you created and carried over the last nine months is so rewarding. A friend of mine gave me this advice and it couldn’t be more true.</li>
</ul>
<p>Aerosmith sums up the infant stage so nicely by saying “Don’t want to close my eyes … and I don’t want to miss a thing” Don’t close your eyes. Memorize her sweet sounds, expressions, and scent. This is such a sacred and special time for the three of you.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>COUNT YOUR MANY BLESSINGS</title>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Parker</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/count-your-many-blessings/"/>
        <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/count-your-many-blessings/</id>

        <updated>2019-07-04T14:11:59-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/8/vNE8214NS9GOvXOy7DCu_DSC_0266-605x402.jpeg" alt="" />
                    This post in much more personal that I would normally write, but&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/8/vNE8214NS9GOvXOy7DCu_DSC_0266-605x402.jpeg" alt="" />
                <p>This post in much more personal that I would normally write, but I feel the need to share my feelings for whatever reason.</p>
<p>Some of you may know this and others may not, but Jack and I have been trying to have a baby for a while now with no success. I have tracked my cycle, started my prenatal vitamins, exercised, and done every other trick in the book to keep my body in the ideal condition for a baby. But, no luck.</p>
<p>Every pregnancy announcement brings me to tears. I feel terrible that all I feel is jealousy and sadness during these wonderful moments of the lives of my friends and family. I remember the first month we started trying I would look down at my belly and whisper sweet things to the baby I thought was growing inside of me. I did this for the following two months because I felt that if I loved and wanted a baby bad enough that it would happen. This only brought more sadness into my life.</p>
<p>I thought that we would for sure be pregnant be Christmas and I could share the wonderful news with friends and family, but that obviously didn’t happen. the next couple of months, I will be able to go to the doctor to figure out why it is that we are having so much trouble getting pregnant. Hopefully, we will find answers that will enable us to grow our family in the near future.</p>
<p>It was so hard for me to understand why this wasn’t happening. Starting a family is a righteous desire and a commandment from the Lord, so why is it that we are having trouble starting a family? After so many months of discouragement, I’m tired of the overwhelming sadness I feel when a new cycle begins and there is still no baby inside of me. I’ve been looking back at the last few months to try to understand why Heavenly Father has withheld the blessing of a child in our lives.</p>
<p>Back in July, Jack and I made the decision to adopt a fur baby since we were having any luck with a real baby. Click here to read the story of how he came into our lives. Calvin keeps me going every day. He brings so much light, energy and happiness into our home and I can’t imagine what our life would be without him. He is my favorite little snuggle bug!</p>
<img class="largeImage" src="http://potspansandparkers.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/walpaper-605x1074.jpg" alt="">
<p>In January we made the decision to start the house hunt again. Walking away from our house last March was so difficult. It was hard to picture our family growing in any other home. We looked at about 7 different houses before we found the one. It could be that if we were pregnant at this time that we wouldn’t have been able to get this perfect house. The house isn’t flashy and elegant, but it is exactly what we want, and I’m excited to start this new chapter of our lives as Homeowners!</p>
<p>One other blessing that we have received is time. Jack and I have had so much time to spend together and strengthen our relationship. It’s nice having this time to be Jack’s wife and supporter. We can go to concerts together, go on last minute road trips and spend our weekends doing whatever we please. Not to mention that we get plenty of sleep.</p>
<p>Maybe a baby isn’t part of Heavenly Father’s plan for us right now, but I am learning to count my blessings in the mean time. Everything happens for a reason, and I am just going to continue enjoying this time with Jack and Calvin.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>CHOCOLATE TURTLE COOKIES</title>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Parker</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/chocolate-turtle-cookies/"/>
        <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/chocolate-turtle-cookies/</id>

        <updated>2019-07-04T13:37:03-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/1/DSC_0057pinterest-01-605x849.jpg" alt="" />
                    Even though the holidays are over, it’s not too late to make&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/1/DSC_0057pinterest-01-605x849.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Even though the holidays are over, it’s not too late to make a batch of these delicious chocolatey cookies. I made these for a church activity about a week ago and they were a huge hit! They are super simple and look gorgeous.</p>
<p>Ingredients</p>
<p><strong>Cookie:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>1 c. all-purpose flour</li>
<li>1/3 c. cocoa powder</li>
<li>1/4 tsp. salt</li>
<li>1 stick butter, softened</li>
<li>2/3 c. sugar</li>
<li>1 large egg, separated, plus 1 additional egg white</li>
<li>2 T. milk</li>
<li>1 tsp. vanilla extract</li>
<li>1/4 tsp. baking soda</li>
<li>1 1/4 c. pecans, finely chopped</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Caramel Filling:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>25 soft caramels, unwrapped</li>
<li>1/3 cup milk or heavy cream</li>
<li>1/3 cup mini marshmallows</li>
<li>optional: 1/2 tsp salt</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Chocolate Drizzle (optional):</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>2 squares of Baker’s Semi-Sweet Baking Chocolate Squares</li>
<li>1 tsp. shortening</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Prepare the Cookies:</strong></p>
<p>1. Combine flour, cocoa, baking soda, and salt; set aside.</p>
<p>2. Beat butter and sugar until light and fluffy, add egg yolk, milk, and vanilla; mix until incorporated. Add flour mixture until just combined.</p>
<p>3. Whisk egg whites (add about a 1 tsp sugar) in a bowl until frothy. Place chopped pecans in another bowl. Roll dough into 1-inch balls, dip in egg whites, and then roll in pecans. Place balls about 2 inches apart on a baking sheet.</p>
<p>4. Bake at 350 degrees until set, about 11 minutes.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Prepare the Caramel Filling:</strong></p>
<p>1. Microwave caramels, marshmallow, and cream together in a small bowl, stirring occasionally, until smooth, about 1 to 2 minutes.</p>
<p>2. Once cookies are removed from the oven, gently press the an indentation with a 1/2 tsp. Fill each indentation with the caramel mixture. Transfer to a wire rack to cool.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Prepare the Chocolate Drizzle (optional):</strong></p>
<p>1. Place chocolate and shortening in a small zip-top plastic bag. Microwave 15 seconds at a time until the mixture is melted.</p>
<p>2. Snip a very small hole in the corner of the plastic bag. Drizzle chocolate over the cooled Turtle Cookies.</p>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>CHOCOLATE CRINKLE COOKIES</title>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Parker</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/chocolate-crinkle-cookies/"/>
        <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/chocolate-crinkle-cookies/</id>

        <updated>2019-07-04T13:39:24-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/2/coverlabel-605x857.jpg" alt="" />
                    I remember when I was younger my mom would be baking in&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/2/coverlabel-605x857.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>I remember when I was younger my mom would be baking in the kitchen and I would do my best to sneak cookies when she wasn’t looking. I was successful a good majority of the time, with the exception of these cookies. The guilty look on my face complimented the powdered sugar around the edges of my mouth.</p>
<p>These gooey bitter chocolate cookies melt in your mouth as they are united with the decadent powdered sugar. YUM YUM YUM! Now let’s get to the recipe!</p>
<ul>
<li>1/2 cup of cocoa powder</li>
<li>1 cup of sugar</li>
<li>1/4 cup of oil</li>
<li>2 eggs</li>
<li>1 tsp of vanilla</li>
<li>1 cup of flour</li>
<li>1 tsp of baking powder</li>
<li>1/4 tsp of salt</li>
<li>1/2 cup of mini semi sweet chocolate chips</li>
<li>1/4 cup of powdered sugar used for coating</li>
</ul>
<p>Combine the cocoa and sugar, mix in oil until the dough is uniform. Add the eggs to the dough one at a time and add vanilla. Sift the flour, baking powder and salt into the dough. Try not to over mix the dough to keep your cookies moist. Mix in chocolate chips.</p>
<p>Chill dough for two hours. Heat oven to 350 degrees. Scoop into 1 inch balls and coat with powdered sugar. Bake cookies for 9 -11 minutes. Enjoy!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>MEET CALVIN</title>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Parker</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/meet-calvin/"/>
        <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/meet-calvin/</id>

        <updated>2019-07-04T14:22:20-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/9/DSC_00601-605x403.jpg" alt="" />
                    A little over a month ago our family grew with the addition&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/9/DSC_00601-605x403.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>A little over a month ago our family grew with the addition of our sweet little Calvin.</p>
<p>Our evening started out just by going to the Oregon Humane Society to check out the dogs and get an idea of what dog would be best for our family, and when we could make it happen (we had no intentions of bringing a dog home that night). Side note, Oregon Humane Society is AMAZING! If you’re looking to adopt an animal, go there first. They are so kind to the animals there and they are so helpful with partnering families with an animal that is the best fit with them.</p>
<p>As we walked through the different rooms we were making a list of all of the dogs that we wanted to meet. We had well over 10 dogs, so we went through the rooms once more to cut down our list to five dogs that we wanted to visit with in the play room. Three of the dogs that we wanted to see were on hold so we knew there was a possibility that they would not be available much longer. We saw two dogs and I was getting discouraged. One was too terrified to come near us and the other was so hyper and peeing on everything and wouldn’t take the time to be with us.  At this point the only dogs we had left on our meet and greet list were on hold for someone who had come in earlier to meet with the dog and possibly thought about adopting them.</p>
<p>Bernard was our third dog, the scruffiest dog in the shelter! He was a rescue that was brought in from Los Angeles and we weren’t given much information about him, just because there wasn’t any. Once we got into the play room I kneeled on the floor to play with Bernard and he crawled into my lap. I was ready to cry and I looked up and Jack and that was the moment that we realized that we would be bringing a dog into our home that night.</p>
<div class="gallery-container"> </div>
<div class="gallery-container">We asked about when Bernard’s hold would expire and that’s when we knew that it was meant to be. We played with him from about 5:20-5:45. The hold expired at 5:35! Yup, he was meant to be a part of our family. After filling out all of the paperwork we were on our way home with our new little doggie!<br><a class="fancybox" href="http://potspansandparkers.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/IMG_2204-e1409174067374.jpg" rel="gallery"></a></div>
<div class="gallery-container"> </div>
<div class="gallery-container">Our first night together was an adventure. We were told specfically not to give him a bath for 48 hours because of some flea medication. Before bed, I took him outside the apartment for a potty break and sure enough we walked right into a giant pile of mud. Needless to say, he had his first bath. as we got ready for bed, we kneeled down by the side of our bed to say a pray. Calvin propped himself up on the bed and joined us in prayer and I cried again. This little doggie was meant to be ours. </div>
<p>After a couple days Jack and I decided to change his name to Calvin. We had a couple of moments when we couldn’t even remember the name Bernard! He made himself at home very quickly.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>ULTIMATE PEANUT BUTTER COOKIES</title>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Parker</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/ultimate-peanut-butter-cookies/"/>
        <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/ultimate-peanut-butter-cookies/</id>

        <updated>2019-07-04T13:49:14-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/3/DSC_0128-2.jpg" alt="" />
                    Stop whatever it is that you are doing right now and go&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/3/DSC_0128-2.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Stop whatever it is that you are doing right now and go buy the biggest bag of Reese’s Pieces that you can find so you can make these scrumptious peanut butter cookies.</p>
<p>This week I told myself that I would go on a mini diet just to drop a couple of pounds real quick, and then I had the genius idea to make these cookies. Ya, that was a great idea right? My diet will just have to wait until next week.</p>
<p>Don’t bother preheating your oven while mixing together these cookies because they need to be refrigerated for about 3 hours before baking.</p>
<p>Ingredients:</p>
<ul>
<li>1 large egg</li>
<li>1 cup packed light brown sugar</li>
<li>3/4 cup creamy peanut butter</li>
<li>1/2 cup unsalted butter (softened)</li>
<li>1 TBSP vanilla extract</li>
<li>1 3/4 cup of flour</li>
<li>pinch of salt</li>
<li>3/4 tsp baking soda</li>
<li>3/4 cup Reese’s Pieces</li>
<li>3/4 cup chocolate chips</li>
</ul>
<p>Directions:</p>
<ol>
<li>Cream together egg, brown sugar, peanut butter,  softened butter and vanilla until the dough has a consistent texture and appearance.</li>
<li>Sift together the flour, salt, and baking soda. Add in the dry flour mixture in small amounts to the wet dough until dough is formed.</li>
<li>Add in the good stuff (reese’s pieces and chocolate chips) and mix on low.</li>
<li>Scoop the cookie dough into large 1.5 inch – 2 inch balls and refrigerate for 2-3 hours.</li>
<li>Preheat your oven to 350 degrees and gently press down the scoops of dough.</li>
<li>Bake for 11-13 minutes.</li>
<li>Enjoy!</li>
</ol>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>WHY I CHOSE TO GET MARRIED AT 18</title>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Parker</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/why-i-chose-to-get-married-at-18/"/>
        <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/why-i-chose-to-get-married-at-18/</id>

        <updated>2019-07-04T14:25:53-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/10/157.jpg" alt="" />
                    I was married to my wonderful husband, Jack, on January 4, 2013&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/10/157.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>I was married to my wonderful husband, Jack, on January 4, 2013 and it was the best decision I have ever made, and I was 18 years old. I had so many rude remarks and judgments placed against me. People told me that I didn’t understand love; I was too young to know what love is. I was told that I was making a bad decision by giving away my teenage years just to become a wife.</p>
<p>What people didn’t understand is that a wife is all I have ever wanted to be. Heck, I don’t even have a particular career field that I want to go in because my plan is to be a mom. I didn’t want to live the typical college student life; I didn’t care for parties, or staying up all night with roommates. And what so many people didn’t understand is that when I found Jack, it was so obvious that I was supposed to marry him. It just happened, I knew that this was the man that I would spend eternity with.</p>
<p>I enjoy cooking meals for my husband, I enjoy folding our laundry, and I love cuddling on the couch discovering new series on Netflix that we then binge watch for the next month. I was done with all of the gossipy girls and talking about each other negatively. It’s so satisfying to know that I have someone on my side that will always have my back and thinks the world of me.</p>
<p>Additional Plus: I married someone who was done with college. I cannot express how wonderful it has been to marry someone who already has a stable job and doesn’t have to balance a job, classes, and our relationship. I see so many couples who struggle trying to get through college together, and I’m not saying that it is impossible, but it makes things a little more complicated.</p>
<p>An update on our Marriage: Jack and I have now been married for a year and two months, and I am very happy with how I see our relationship grow through challenges and blessings. We have seen so many blessings from our Heavenly Father lately resulting in us growing closer together. We recently put in an offer on a house and it was accepted, so we are now in the processes of buying a home. We are looking forward to trying to start a family in the near future in our new home!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>ORANGE CREAMSICLE COOKIES FROM HEAVEN</title>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Parker</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/orange-creamsicle-cookies-from-heaven/"/>
        <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/orange-creamsicle-cookies-from-heaven/</id>

        <updated>2019-07-04T14:02:15-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/6/DSC_0008-605x756.jpg" alt="" />
                    One of my favorite treats when I was growing up were those&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/6/DSC_0008-605x756.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>One of my favorite treats when I was growing up were those cups of ice cream that had the wax covered lid with a wooden spoon and they came with different syrups swirled in. And my favorite by far was the orange creamsicle cup! Talk about delicious! So, putting it in a cookie form made perfect sense, all of the flavors of the yummy ice cream cup in the form of a warm gooey cookie.</p>
<p>Orange Creamsicle Cookies</p>
<ul>
<li>2 1/2 cups of flour</li>
<li>3/4 tsp of baking soda</li>
<li>1/2 tsp of salt</li>
<li>2 sticks of softened butter</li>
<li>1/2 cup of sugar</li>
<li>1/2 cup of firmly packed brown sugar</li>
<li>1 large egg</li>
<li>1 tsp of vanilla</li>
<li>3-4 TBSP of orange zest (about 2 oranges)</li>
<li>1 1/2 cups of white chocolate chips</li>
</ul>
<p>Preheat your oven to 375 degrees. Cream together the butter, sugar and brown sugar until smooth. Beat in egg and vanilla. Mix in salt and baking soda. Gradually add in small amounts of flour until dough is homogenous. Stir in orange zest and white chips. Cook for 8 to 10 minutes.</p>
<p>My husbands comment on these cookies “This recipe is a keeper babe!” I don’t even want to mention how many I ate before they had even cooled… I’ll just let you figure that out on your own.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>SOME MORE S’MORES</title>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Parker</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/some-more-smores/"/>
        <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/some-more-smores/</id>

        <updated>2019-08-23T20:45:57-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/5/DSC_0425-282x412-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    As fun as roasting marshmallows over an open fire is, I prefer&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/5/DSC_0425-282x412-1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>As fun as roasting marshmallows over an open fire is, I prefer to make s’mores pan style. There are super fast and so delicious!</p>
<p>Pan Style S’mores</p>
<ul>
<li>10-12 graham crackers (crushed)</li>
<li>1 bag of mini marshmallows</li>
<li>3-4 TBS of butter</li>
<li>3 chocolate bars</li>
</ul>
<p>You're basically making rice krispie treats, but I'll break in down for you. Melt the butter over medium heat. Add in the marshmallows and stir until they have melted. Add in your crushed graham crackers and stir, stir, stir. Press the mixture into a 8x10 pan and top with some ooey gooey chocolate.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>COMPETITION WORTHY BANANA BREAD</title>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Parker</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/competition-worthy-banana-bread/"/>
        <id>https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/competition-worthy-banana-bread/</id>

        <updated>2019-07-04T13:55:35-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/4/DSC_03761-605x354.jpg" alt="" />
                    One of the first conversations that Jack and I had was about&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://katiejparker.github.io/potspansandparkers/media/posts/4/DSC_03761-605x354.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>One of the first conversations that Jack and I had was about this banana bread. He suggested that we have a banana bread bake off with my best recipe against this one. The competition never happened, but Jack brought me a loaf of his banana bread for dessert when I made him dinner on our second date. And I have to say that it was unbelievable! It’s dense and very flavorful. His secret ingredient, pudding mix. Who knew?</p>
<p>Banana Bread</p>
<ul>
<li>1/2 cup of shortening</li>
<li>3/4 cup of sugar</li>
<li>2 eggs</li>
<li>3/4 cup of mashed bananas (about 2-3 bananas beginning to brown)</li>
<li>1 package of vanilla instant pudding mix</li>
<li>1 1/4 cup of flour</li>
<li>3/4 tsp baking soda</li>
<li>1/2 tsp of salt</li>
</ul>
<p>First, cream together shortening and sugar, gently mix in eggs 1 at a time. Mix in bananas until the badder is thick and slightly chunky. In a separate bowl mix all of the dry ingredients and sift. Slowly add in the sifted dry indigents into the wet mixture.  Be sure to spray and flour your bread pan before placing the badder into the pan. Bake at 350 degree for around 45-50 minutes. Stick a toothpick in the middle of the bread to check the progress. When the toothpick comes out clean, your bread is ready to come out and cool down. Serve warm with butter.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
